JOSE GREGORIO ROMERO MENDOZA

E-mail: jgromerom89@gmail.com

E-mail: jrdevs@cyberzon3.com

Tel: +54 91134635997

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jose-gregorio-romero-1a83217a/

Github: https://github.com/chechesk
Briefcase: https://jrdevs.cyberzon3.com/

Full Stack Engineer

I am a Full Stack Engineer with experience in developing web and mobile applications. During my professional career, I worked on a variety of projects and technologies, which has allowed me to acquire solid skills in the field of software engineering. Currently, I work as a Full Stack Engineer at Tres Pagos, where I work in a remote environment using technologies such as Firebase, NextJs, TypeScript.

Technologies

NodeJs

- Express
- Docker

- Firebase
- JavaScript
- Docker Compose

- PostgresSQL
- Git GitHub
- Google Cloud

- MongoDB
- Tailwind
- React

- Wordpress
- Elementor Pro
- React SEO

- Hubspot
- Cloudinary
- Redux

Experience

Bootcamp SoyHenry ("Group Project").

August 2022 - June 2023 (11 months)

Participate in the development of a 100% functional ecommerce and scalable to where the client wants In this project I will learn to work as a team in addition to participate in the frontend and backend area using React, Redux, CSS, JavaScript among others in the frontend and in the back using vite, typescript, mongodb, mongoose making related models or scalable and

modifiable REST API routes as you go expanding requirements or resources. (it is an academic

Project However, it helps me work as a team and practice git flow)

here I leave you the project

https://www.cyberzon3.com/

Full Stack Developer ("SoyHenry Project Individuality)

"Project Food" Program | February 2023 - March 2023 (1 months)

Development of an application tends to be implemented by receiving the information

through an API to receive the list of recipes, which are consulted and if I register my own recipe

stored in the designed backend. Back shown on the front making a list of cards, JavaScript, Redux,

HTML, CSS, NodeJs and other technologies. Exhibition of the functionalities required for the

sprints in weekly demonstrations.

Force Seals Security Sac

IT Technician March 2023 - August 2023 (6 months) Lima, Perú

Implementation of server policies and domain control. Verify the integrity of the network

and all equipment. Supervise that all in-person and remote stations are fully operational.

Open Tecnologies

Store Manager

February 2019 - July 2022 (3 years 6 months)

Lima Peru

Manage the functions of the assigned store, carry out sales management and advice on

the products offered by the brand. Check the stock or physical inventory and by series of the

products registered in the inventory. Make cash balance, cover pending payment functions for

services acquired by the store.

Solusoft Peru SAC

Software Implementation Specialist

July 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 1 month)

San Miguel, Lima, Peru

Implementation of Visifact Billing Software set in SQL Server, on Windows operating

system, with implementation of local and remote terminals with IP or VPN connection

Education

Microservice – Henry Bootcamp

September 2023 - October 2023

MongoDB – Docker – Docker Compose - Microservice

Full Stack Developer Henry bootcamp

January 2022 - September 2023

HTML - CSS - JavaScrip - ReactJs - Redux - NodeJs - Express - PostgreSQL

IUTA, Information technology

(julio de 2009 - julio de 2012)